http://www.bibleschools.com/legal-notice?locale=en

LanguagesHomeAboutContactSign InLegal NoticeAll information on this website is copyrighted by the Voice of
Prophecy. All rights are reserved. United States copyright law
protects all materials contained on this site. By using this site,
you acknowledge that the Voice of Prophecy owns all intellectual
property rights in and to the site and its contents and that these
rights are valid and protected in all forms. You may not modify,
remove, delete, augment, add to, exploit, publish, transmit,
participate in the transfer or sale of, and/or create derivative
works from the content either in whole or in part.The Voice of Prophecy will not sell or distribute any information,
including personal or identifying information, which is obtained
through your use of this website. The Voice of Prophecy is not
gathering such information, but may obtain such information by your
communication directly with the website's Webmaster. Any names or
information provided by users of the website shall only be used for
the purpose such information is provided.The Voice of Prophecy is providing this website for your information
purposes only. Certain organizations may choose to link this website
to their own website. Such linkage is not meant to imply that the
Voice of Prophecy agrees with, supports, or concurs with the content
such websites may contain. THE VOICE OF PROPHECY IS PROVIDING THIS
SITE AND ITS CONTENTS "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY OBLIGATIONS, LIABILITIES,
OR WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WHATSOEVER TO ANYONE WHO CHOOSES
TO ACCESS THIS WEBSITE. EACH USER EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGES THAT USE OF
THIS WEBSITE AND ITS CONTENTS IS AT THE USER'S SOLE RISK. THE VOICE
OF PROPHECY DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THIS WEBSITE OR ANY OF ITS
CONTENTS WILL BE CONTINUOUSLY AVAILABLE, ACCESSIBLE, NON-INFRINGING,
OR FREE OF ERRORS OR VIRUSES OR ANYTHING ELSE MANIFESTING
CONTAMINATING OR DESTRUCTIVE PROPERTIES, OR THAT THE INFORMATION
CONTAINED IN IT IS ACCURATE OR RELIABLE. THE VOICE OF PROPHECY WILL
NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY (INCLUDING INDIRECT,
SPECIAL, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES) THAT MAY RESULT FROM THE USE OF
OR INABILITY TO USE ANY PART OF THE WEBSITE, OR FROM ANYTHING
SUBMITTED OR POSTED BY USERS. THE TERMS OF THIS PARAGRAPH WILL
SURVIVE ANY TERMINATION OF THIS NOTICE AND WEBSITE.This site is created and controlled under the laws of the State of
Colorado, which shall be the law giving effect to and interpretation
of all terms and conditions hereunder. Any action pertaining to this
website shall be in the State of Colorado with Larimer County the
venue for such action. Any person named a party to any action
regarding this website agrees to submit to the exclusive
jurisdiction of the courts of the State of Colorado and of the
United States of America located in the State of Colorado.For further information regarding this website or anything related
to it, you may e-mail webmaster@vop.com or write to:Voice of ProphecyAttention: WebmasterBox 999Loveland, CO 80539-0999Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)Children's Information May be Received and Retained with Consent,
but No Third Party SharingThe Internet, as a widespread and often readily available resource,
presents a host of possibilities and challenges for young users. We
understand this, and are committed to providing an online experience
for children that is safe and rewarding. In accordance with the
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we strive to
safeguard the privacy of children who visit our website. Personal
information is defined under COPPA as "individually identifiable
information," information that helps others to identify a particular
person. The following is information about data we may collect, how
we use it, who has access to it, and what parents' and legal
guardians' rights are with regard to the collection, storage, and
use of their child's personal information.Visitors to our website under age 13 are for the most part free to
access the various features our site offers without disclosing any
personal information. From time to time, however, we offer
interactive programs and activities that may require children to
disclose personal information in order to participate. We may also
request personal information for demographic interests and research
to help us provide for our parents and children. Children will not
be required to disclose any more personal information than is
reasonably necessary to participate in a program or activity. The
information required may include the child's name, e-mail address,
age, mailing address, along with other personal data.Before children under age 13 will be permitted to disclose personal
information to participate in any programs or activities, we require
consent from a parent or legal guardian. In order to do this, we
will ask the child to provide his or her first and last name and
e-mail address, as well as the e-mail address of a parent or legal
guardian. With this information, we will e-mail the parent or legal
guardian and request consent for the collection and use of the
child's personal information. Parents or legal guardians may give
their consent by completing a consent form and returning it by mail
or facsimile. Parents or legal guardians may also choose to give
consent simply by e-mailing us directly. If parents or legal
guardians choose this option, we will verify their e-mailed consent
by follow-up letter, telephone call or e-mail. Once consent is
given, the child will be permitted to participate.Parents or legal guardians who provide consent to the collection and
use of their child's personal information may revoke that consent at
any time. They may also review and edit their child's information
and request that information be deleted at any time. Parents or
legal guardians who have any other questions or concerns about our
privacy policy, who wish to revoke consent to the collection and use
of their child's information and stop all future collection of that
information, or who wish to review and/or delete their child's
information may contact our Webmaster by e-mail at webmaster@vop.com, by telephone at (970) 622-2999 or by mail at Box 999,
Loveland, CO 80539. Parents or legal guardians must also verify
their identity and relationship to the child by providing their
name, address, and stated legal relationship to the child.Use of CookiesBesides sponsoring programs that may require the disclosure of
personal information for participation, we may also use special
technology called "cookies." Cookies are test files that contain
pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's
hard disk. They can be useful for record-keeping purposes and help
us to tailor our Web site to the interests and needs of our
visitors. Cookies may also be used to increase session security. We
do not in any way use this information to personally identify
individual users.Copyright 2020 Voice of Prophecy. All rights reserved. Legal Notice. Teacher Login
